<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
	xmlns:w="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets"
	xmlns:tbl="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables"
	>
	<ui:with field='GDStr' type='com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.ui.PA_UI.GenderDependantStrings'/>
	<ui:style>	
		
	</ui:style>
	
	<g:HTMLPanel>
		<table>
		<col style="width:15ex"/><col /><col style="width:43ex"/>
			<tr>
				<td>Investigator's conclusions</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}"/></td>
				<td>Provide a brief paragraph of the investigator's conclusions.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Agency Comments</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" height="45ex"/></td>
				<td>
					<ul style="padding-left:0px;margin-left:2ex;">Briefly summarize the results and discuss the following:<!-- class="zeroDistance" -->
						<li>Evaluate the adequacy of the dose levels tested.</li> 
						<li>Discuss the systemic toxicity observed (i.e., survival, body weight, body weight gain, target organ toxicity etc).</li>
						<li>Was age and weight at preputial separation within acceptable ranges? Report findings relative to performance criteria?</li>
						<li>Were there any changes in organ weights compared to controls?  Report findings relative to performance criteria?</li>
						<li>Were there any effects on hormone levels?</li>
						<li>Were there any effects on clinical chemistry parameters?</li>
						<li>Were there any changes in histopathological findings?</li>
					</ul>
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Study Deficiencies</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}"/></td>
				<td>List each deviation from the protocol and classify the deviation as major or
				minor.  Also report any rationale provided by the investigator for the deviation.
				Similarly list, classify, and discuss all other deficiencies with the conduct,
				results, and reporting of the study.  Discuss the possibility of resolving
				the deficiencies and what would be required.  Major deficiencies may be presented
				and discussed in paragraph form, whereas minor deficiencies can be presented
				in a bulleted list.</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 