<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
	xmlns:w="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets"
	
	xmlns:tbl="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables"
	>
	<ui:style>	
		
	</ui:style>
	<ui:with field='GDStr' type='com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.ui.PA_UI.GenderDependantStrings'/>
	
	<g:HTMLPanel width="110ex">
		<table>
			<col style="width:30ex"/><col/><col style="width:40ex"/>
			<tr>
				<td style="text-decoration:underline">Dose Preparation and Analysis</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Dose formulations were prepared
					daily by mixing appropriate
					amounts of test substance with
				</td>
				<td><w:DERTextBoxLength name="{GDStr.getPath}"/></td>
				<td>Vehicle.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Homogeneity and stability were tested at</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>State when, what dose levels, duration, and temperature.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>During the study, samples of
					dose formulations were analyzed
					for achieved concentration.</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>State when and at what dose levels.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td style="text-decoration:underline">Results of Dose Analysis
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Homogeneity:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Concentration range as percent of nominal and/or coefficient of variation for different strata (e.g., top, middle, and bottom).</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Stability:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Range of values for each temperature and duration tested, expressed as percent of initial (preferable) or percent of nominal concentration.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Concentration:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Range of values expressed as percent of nominal.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td colspan="3">The analytical data indicated that the mixing procedure was adequate.
				<w:DERListBoxYesNo name="{GDStr.getPath}"/></td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td colspan="3">And that the variation between nominal and actual dosage to the animals was acceptable.
				<w:DERListBoxYesNo name="{GDStr.getPath}"/></td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Describe any deficiencies noted.</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>				
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td style="text-decoration:underline">Dosage Administration
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>All doses were administered once
					daily by gavage from PND 23
					through PND53,in a volume of</td>
				<td><w:DERTextBoxLength name="{GDStr.getPath}" visibleLength='9'/>&nbsp;mL/kg of body weight</td>
				<td>Recommended range from 2.5 to 5.0.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Dosing was performed daily between</td>
				<td><w:DERTextBoxLength name="{GDStr.getPath}" visibleLength='9'>0700
					</w:DERTextBoxLength>&nbsp;and
					<w:DERTextBoxLength name="{GDStr.getPath}" visibleLength='9'>0900
					</w:DERTextBoxLength>
					&nbsp;hours</td>
				<td></td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Statistics:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" /></td>
				<td>The following describes the statistical analyses recommended by the test
					guideline and may be used by the reviewer for verification.
					The DER should list parameters that were analyzed and the statistical methods
					used and include a statement as to whether or not the Reviewer considers
					the analyses to be appropriate. If inappropriate, provide alternative/rationale.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td colspan="3">
				The data should be analyzed for normal distribution and homogeneity of variance in order to satisfy the assumptions of
				Analysis of Variance (ANOVA) and Analysis of Covariance (ANCOVA)). It is recommended that all data
				(i.e., initial body weight [PND 23], body weight gain, age and body weight at preputial separation, terminal body weight,
				organ weights, and serum hormones be analyzed by ANOVA.  If the study was conducted in blocks, then the recommended analysis
				is to use to a two-way ANOVA with Block and Treatment as main effects.  It is recommended age and body weight at preputial
				separation and all organ weights also be analyzed by ANCOVA, using the body weight at PND 23 as the covariate.
				When statistically significant effects among groups are observed (p&lt;0.05), appropriate pair-wise comparison tests
				would be needed in order to identify which dose group is significantly different from the control group.
				Where there is heterogeneity of variance, data should be transformed appropriately to achieve homogeneous variances prior to ANOVA/ANCOVA,
				or analyzed using an appropriate nonparametric test.  However, non parametric analysis would generally be the method of last resort
				as it does not allow analysis of covariance.  In addition to ANOVA and ANCOVA, it is recommended that the unadjusted and adjusted
				values be examined for linear trend with dose level.
				</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 