<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
	xmlns:w="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets"
	xmlns:tbl="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables"
	>
	<ui:style>	
		
	</ui:style>
	<ui:with field='GDStr' type='com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.ui.PA_UI.GenderDependantStrings'/>
	
	<g:HTMLPanel width="110ex">
		<table>
			<col style="width:20ex"/><col /><col style="width:45ex"/>
			<tr>
				<td>Dose Selection Rationale</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}">
					<p>	The dose levels were selected based on the results from a range-finding study
						(MRID <span style="color:firebrick">[#]</span>) in which <span style="color:firebrick">[15]</span>
						rats/sex/dose group were administered the test substance in corn oil via gavage at doses of 0, 500,
						or 1000 mg/kg/day from PND <span style="color:firebrick">[23 53]</span>.
						At 1000 mg/kg/day, body weights were significantly decreased by 15 18% (p&lt;0.05)
						compared to controls beginning on PND 42, resulting in a decrease of 16% p&lt;0.05)
						in terminal body weight.  Body weights at 500 mg/kg/day were comparable to controls
						throughout the study.  There were no mortalities, clinical signs of toxicity,
						or effects on BUN or creatinine at either dose.
					</p>
					</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
				</td>
				<td>Briefly describe any range-finding study, including information regarding the study identification
				(laboratory report or MRID number), study type (i.e., duration, route of administration,
				species), dose levels, effects, and conclusions.  The guideline recommends that the highest
				dose level be at or just below the Maximum Tolerated Dose (MTD) but need not exceed the Limit Dose
				(1000 mg/kg/day).			
				</td>
			</tr> 
			<tr>
				<td colspan="3">However, typically, the Agency also considers the toxicity profile
				of the chemical (i.e., cholinesterase inhibition, target organ toxicity, etc.) in dose selection.
				The second dose level should typically be spaced to produce a lesser degree of toxicity relative
				to the high dose unless justification is provided for testing at a different level.
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Dose Preparation and Analysis</td>
				<td>
					<w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}">
					<p>Dose formulations were prepared daily by mixing appropriate amounts of
					test substance with <span style="color:firebrick">[vehicle]</span>.
					Homogeneity and stability were tested at
					<span style="color:firebrick;font-style:italic">(state when, what dose levels, duration, and temperature)</span>.
					During the study, samples of dose formulations were analyzed
					<span style="color:firebrick;font-style:italic">(state when and at what dose levels)</span>
					for achieved concentration.
					</p>
					</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td style="text-decoration:underline" colspan="3">Results of Dose Analysis
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Homogeneity:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Concentration range as percent of nominal and/or coefficient of variation for different strata (e.g., top, middle, and bottom).</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Stability:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Range of values for each temperature and duration tested, expressed as percent of initial (preferable) or percent of nominal concentration.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Concentration:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Range of values expressed as percent of nominal.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td colspan="3">The analytical data indicated that the mixing procedure 
				<w:DERListBoxSC name="{GDStr.getPath}">
				    <g:item>was</g:item><g:item>was not</g:item>
				</w:DERListBoxSC>
				adequate. 
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td colspan="3">And that the variation between nominal and actual dosage to the animals
				<w:DERListBoxSC name="{GDStr.getPath}">
				    <g:item>was</g:item><g:item>was not</g:item>
				</w:DERListBoxSC>
				acceptable.
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Describe any deficiencies noted.</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>				
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Dosage Administration</td>
				<td>
					<w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}">
					<p>All doses were administered once daily by gavage from PND 23 through PND 53,
					    in a volume of <span style="color:firebrick">[#]</span> mL/kg of body weight.
						Dosing was performed between <span style="color:firebrick">[0700] and [0900]</span> hours daily.
					</p>
					</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
				</td>
				<td>Recommended range for dose volume is from 2.5 to 5.0 mL/kg of body weight.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Statistics:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" /></td>
				<td>The following describes the statistical analyses recommended by the test
					guideline and may be used by the reviewer for verification.
					The DER should list parameters that were analyzed and the statistical methods
					used and include a statement as to whether or not the Reviewer considers
					the analyses to be appropriate. If inappropriate, provide alternative/rationale.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td colspan="3">The data should be analyzed for normal distribution and homogeneity of
				    variance in order to satisfy the assumptions of Analysis of Variance (ANOVA)
				    and Analysis of Covariance (ANCOVA)). It is recommended that all data
				    (i.e., initial body weight [PND 23], body weight gain, age and body weight at preputial separation,
				    terminal body weight, organ weights, and serum hormones be analyzed by ANOVA.
				    If the study was conducted in blocks, then the recommended analysis is to use to a two-way
				    ANOVA with Block and Treatment as main effects.  It is recommended age and body weight at
				    preputial separation and all organ weights also be analyzed by ANCOVA,
				    using the body weight at PND 23 as the covariate.  When statistically significant effects
				    among groups are observed (p&lt;0.05), appropriate pair-wise comparison tests would be needed in
				    order to identify which dose group is significantly different from the control group.
				     Where there is heterogeneity of variance, data should be transformed appropriately to
				     achieve homogeneous variances prior to ANOVA/ANCOVA, or analyzed using an appropriate
				     nonparametric test.  However, non parametric analysis would generally be the method of last
				     resort as it does not allow analysis of covariance.  In addition to ANOVA and ANCOVA,
				     it is recommended that the unadjusted and adjusted values be examined for linear trend with dose level.
				</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 