<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
	xmlns:w="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets"
	xmlns:tbl="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables"
	xmlns:tbl_hersh="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables.hersh"
	>
	<ui:style>		
	</ui:style>
	
	<g:HTMLPanel width="105ex">
		<table>
		    <col/><col/><col/>
		    <tr>
		       <td>Dose Selection Rationale</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>DoseSelectionRationale>>Html">
				    <p>The dose levels were selected based on the results from a range-finding study
				    (<span style="color:firebrick">MRID No.</span>) in which six castrated male rats/dose group were
				    administered the test substance in corn oil via gavage at doses of 0, 100, 300, or 1000 mg/kg/day
				    for 10 days.  At 300 mg/kg/day, weights of the ventral prostate, seminal vesicles,
				    and LABC were significantly (p&lt;0.05) increased over vehicle controls.
				    Additionally at 1000 mg/kg/day, glans penis weight was increased.  Based on these findings, doses lower
				    than 300 mg/kg/day were used for the main study.</p>
				 </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT></td>
				 <td>Briefly describe any range-finding study, including information regarding the study
				     identification (laboratory report or MRID number), study type (i.e., duration, route of
				     administration, species), dose levels, effects, and conclusions.
				     The highest dose level does not need to exceed the limit dose of 1000 mg/kg/day.
				  </td>  
		    </tr>
		    <tr>
		        <td>Dose Preparation</td>
		        <td>
		            <w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>DosePreparation>>Html">
		                <p>Dose formulations were prepared <span style="color:firebrick">[daily or prior to treatment]</span>
		                by mixing appropriate amounts of test substance with <span style="color:firebrick">[type of vehicle/solvent]</span>.
		                Doses were adjusted daily based on individual body weight measurements.
		                Homogeneity and stability were tested at <span style="color:firebrick">[when, what dose levels, duration,
		                and temperature]</span>.  During the study, samples of dose formulations were analyzed
		                <span style="color:firebrick">[when and at what dose levels]</span> for achieved concentration.</p>
		            </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
		        </td>
		        <td>Information on dose formulations should include:
		            method and frequency of preparation (i.e., for each dose formulation OR via serial dilution,
		            etc.); storage conditions (i.e., duration and temperature); and dose analysis
		            for homogeneity (sampling method); stability (storage temperature and duration)
		            and achieved concentration (dose levels and when analyzed).
		        </td>  
		    </tr>
		   <tr>
				<td style="text-decoration:underline" colspan="3">Results of Dose Analysis
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Homogeneity:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>Homogeneity>>Html" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Concentration range as percent of nominal and/or coefficient of variation for different strata (e.g., top, middle, and bottom).</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Stability:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>Stability>>Html" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Range of values for each temperature and duration tested, expressed as percent of initial (preferable) or percent of nominal concentration.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Concentration:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>Concentration>>Html" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Range of values expressed as percent of nominal.</td>
			</tr>
		    <tr>
				<td colspan="3">The analytical data indicated that the mixing procedure 
				<w:DERListBoxSC name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>AdequateProcedure"><g:item>was</g:item><g:item>was not</g:item></w:DERListBoxSC>
				adequate. 
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td colspan="3">And that the variation between nominal and actual dosage to the animals
				<w:DERListBoxSC name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>AcceptableVariation"><g:item>was</g:item><g:item>was not</g:item></w:DERListBoxSC>
				acceptable.
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Describe any deficiencies noted.</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>Deficiencies>>Html" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>				
			</tr>
		   <tr>
				<td>Dosage Administration</td>
				<td>
					<w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>DosageAdministration>>Html">
					    <p>Test formulations were administered to the animals daily via oral gavage (5 mL/kg bw)
					        for 10 days.  TP was given via sc injection at 0.5 mL/kg bw, and flutamide was
					        administered via oral gavage at 5 mL/kg bw.  Dose volumes were adjusted daily based
					        on the concurrent body weight measurement.
					    </p>
					</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
				</td>
				<td>
				    Summarize dose administration information regarding the test formulations, TP,
				    and flutamide, including the route of administration, dose schedule, and dose volume.
				    TP should have been administered by subcutaneous (s.c.) injection,
				    and flutamide via oral gavage.  The test substance may be administered via oral gavage or s.c. injection.
				    Animals should have been dosed for 10 consecutive days at approximately 24-hour intervals,				   
				</td>
		    </tr>
		    <tr>
			    <td colspan='3'>with the dose level adjusted daily based body weight. The dose volume for oral gavage administration should not exceed
				    10 mL/kg body weight for aqueous solutions or 5 mL/kg for oil suspensions or solutions.
				    For subcutaneous injection administration, doses should not exceed 0.5 mg/kg body weight.
			    </td>
			</tr>
		    <tr>
				<td>Statistics:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>Statistics>>Html" /></td>
				<td>
				   	Describe the statistical methods used.  Include a statement as to whether or not the Reviewer
				   	considers the analyses used to be appropriate; if inappropriate, provide alternative/rationale.
				   	If inappropriate refer to the guideline for the correct statistical methods and perform
				   	the required analysis.  Refer to SEP for details.  The criterion for statistical significance
				   	should be identified (e.g., p &le; 0.05),			   	
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
			    <td colspan='3'>and groups attaining statistical significance should be denoted. In the DER tables, the asterisk (*) is used as a means of indicating statistical significance.
			        Summary data tables, reporting mean, standard deviation, and CV for each of the organ weights
				   	should be included in the DER for each assay. Examples of these tables are included in the results section of this DER template.
				</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>