<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
	xmlns:w="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets"
	
	xmlns:tbl="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables"
	xmlns:tbl_hersh="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables.hersh"
	>
	<ui:style>		
	</ui:style>
	
	<g:HTMLPanel width="100ex">
	    <table>
	        <col/><col/><col/>
	        <tr>
	            <td>Clinical Examinations</td>
	            <td>
	                <w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ClinicalExaminations>>Html">
	                    <p>Cage-side checks for mortality, moribundity, and clinical signs of toxicity were
	                        conducted twice daily.  Detailed physical examinations were performed prior to
	                        initiation of dosing and at termination.</p>
	                </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
	            </td>
	            <td>
	                Describe the frequency and scope of clinical observations (i.e., cage-side check,
	                hand-held physical examination, and/or standard arena assessment).
	                Clinical observations should have been conducted at least once daily for mortality and signs of toxicity.
	            </td>
	        </tr>
	        <tr>
	            <td>Body Weight</td>
	            <td>
	                <w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>BodyWeight>>Html">
	                    <p>Animals were weighed at randomization, study initiation, day of castration and daily throughout the dosing period.</p>
	                </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
	            </td>
	            <td>Describe the frequency of body weights measurement.
	                Beginning just prior to initiation of treatment, animals should have been individually weighed
	                each day to determine both dose volume and effects of treatment on the animals.
	            </td>
	        </tr>
	        <tr>
	            <td>Food Consumption</td>
	            <td>
	                <w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>FoodConsumption>>Html">
	                    <p>Food consumption was measured for each cage by subtracting the amount of food remaining
	                        in the cage from the amount supplied, accounting for spillage.
	                        Values were reported as group mean daily food consumption (g/animal/day).</p>
	                </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
	            </td>
	            <td>
	                Food consumption measurements (on a cage basis) are optional.
	                If conducted, food consumption should be expressed as g/animal/day.
	            </td>
	        </tr>
	        <tr>
	            <td>Serum Hormone Measurements</td>
	            <td>
	                <w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>SerumHormMeasurements>>Html">
	                    <p>At study termination, each animal was anesthetized with 
	                         <span style="color:firebrick">[method of anesthesia]</span>, and blood was collected via
	                         <span style="color:firebrick">[method/location; <span style="font-style:italic">e.g., the lateral tail</span>]</span>
	                        for serum hormone analyses.  Testosterone (T), luteinizing hormone (LH), and
	                        follicle stimulating hormone (FSH) were measured using radioimmunoassay
	                         <span style="color:firebrick">[kit name, company name location]</span>.</p>
	                </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
	            </td>
	            <td>
	                Serum hormone measurements are optional, but may be useful in elucidating potential treatment
	                related effects.  If the performing laboratory measured serum hormone levels, the reviewers
	                should include information regarding the:  hormones measured; method of anesthesia; blood
	                collection; serum preparation; and analytical procedures (e.g., radioimmunoassay).
	            </td>
	        </tr>
	        <tr>
	            <td> Dissection and Measurement of Tissue and Organ Weights</td>
	            <td>
	                 <w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>Dissection>>Html">
	                     <p>
	                         On PND <span style="color:firebrick">[#]</span> (approximately 24 hours after
	                         the final administration of the test substance), all surviving animals were euthanized
	                         <span style="color:firebrick">[describe method]</span>, exsanguinated, and subjected
	                         to a gross necropsy. The five mandatory androgen-dependent organs (ventral prostate, seminal vesicles,
	                         LABC, Cowper???s gland, and glans penis) were excised, trimmed free of adhering tissue,
	                         and weighed fresh (unfixed) according to the standard operating procedures detailed
	                         in the U.S. EPA Guideline (OCSPP 890.1400).  Additionally, the liver, kidneys,
	                         and adrenals were weighed.
	                     </p>
	                 </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
	            </td>
	            <td>
	                Describe the procedures at study termination, including euthanasia, necropsy, measurement of
	                mandatory and optional organ weights, and any optional histopathology.
	                Individual data for organ weights should have been reported to the nearest 0.1 mg.	                
	            </td>
	        </tr>
	        <tr>
	            <td colspan='3'>
	                Unless there are deviations from the standard operating procedures, it is generally unnecessary
	                to provide more than a brief summary of the methods for dissection and weighing of mandatory
	                accessory sex organs.  Note any deviations from the Test Guideline, especially any procedures that
	                may add to variability in organ weights and impact the performance criteria
	                (e.g., loss of fluids, desiccation, etc.).
	            </td>
	        </tr>
	    </table>
	
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>