<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
	xmlns:w="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets"
	
	xmlns:tbl="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables"
	xmlns:tbl_hersh="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables.hersh"
	>
	<ui:style>	
		
	</ui:style>
	
	<g:HTMLPanel width="121ex">
	<table>
		<col style="width:15ex"/><col/><col style="width:36ex"/>
		<tr>
			<td>In-Life Dates:</td>
			<td style="text-align:center">Start:&nbsp;<w:DERTextBoxLength name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>[0]InLife>>InLifeStart" visibleLength='15'/>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;End:&nbsp;<w:DERTextBoxLength name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>[0]InLife>>InLifeEnd" visibleLength='15'/>
			</td>
			<td>Month/Day/Year</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
		    <td></td>
			<td style="text-align:center">Start:&nbsp;<w:DERTextBoxLength name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>[1]InLife>>InLifeStart" visibleLength='15'/>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;
				&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;End:&nbsp;<w:DERTextBoxLength name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>[1]InLife>>InLifeEnd" visibleLength='15'/>
			</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Study Design:</td>
			<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>StudyDesign>>Html" addStyleNames='bigRTA'>
			    <p>In a Hershberger Assay conducted to screen for the potential anti androgenic activity,
			    the test substance was administered daily via <span style="color:firebrick">[oral gavage or s.c.]</span>
			    to castrated male rats in conjunction with a daily dose of TP (<span style="color:firebrick">[#]</span> mg/kg/day)
			    by sc injection. Anti androgenic activity is indicated by a statistically significant decrease
			    in two or more target organ weights of the treated groups (test substance + TP) compared to
			    the TP only control group.  Additionally, in a Hershberger Assay conducted to screen for potential androgenic activity,
			    the test substance was administered daily via <span style="color:firebrick">[oral gavage or s.c.]</span>
			    castrated male rats.  Positive androgenic activity is defined as a significant increase in two or
			    more organ weights compared to the vehicle control.  For both assays, the animals were dosed for
			    10 consecutive days and necropsied approximately 24 hours after the final dose administration
			    for organ weight measurements.</p>
			   </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT></td>
			 <td>Summarize the study design, including information regarding whether the assay was
			     testing for anti androgenic and androgenic activity, the purpose of each of the treatment groups,
			     and the interpretation of the data. Note any deficiencies in the design and discuss the impact on
			     interpretation and acceptability of the study in the study deficiency section at the end of the DER.
			     <!-- Alter the text as necessary according to the purpose and methodology of the performing laboratory. -->
			 </td>	    
		</tr>
		<tr>
			<td>Study Schedule:</td>
			<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>StudySchedule>>Html" addStyleNames='bigRTA'>
			    <p>Following the initial 7-day acclimation period, sexually mature male rats were castrated on
			        PND 42 according to standard procedures and allowed 7 days for recovery and regression of
			        accessory sex organ weights prior to initiation of dosing.  The dose administration period
			        was from PND 49 through PND 60.  Rats were euthanized on PND 61approximately 24 hours after
			        the last dose and necropsied for organ weight measurements.
			   </p>
			</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT></td>
			<td>
			    Summarize study schedule information regarding age of animals at castration,
			    dosing initiation, and termination.  Note any concerns or deviations from the guideline that may
			    impact the study.  Sprague Dawley and Wistar are the preferred strain of rat.  Refer to the SEP
			    for guidance on other strains.
			</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
		    <td>Animal Assignment:</td>
		    <td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>AnimalAssignment>>Html" addStyleNames='bigRTA'>
		        <p>Animals were assigned, stratified by body weight, to the test groups noted in Table 1.
		            Statistical analysis indicated that there were no significant differences in
		            group means at study initiation.  Furthermore, the body weight of each animal
		            was within 20% of the overall mean.</p>
		    </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT></td>
		    <td>
		        Describe procedures for animal assignment (including factors such as randomization,
		        blocking by body weight, or day of assignment to allow for staggered necropsy).
		        Note if animals were within acceptable criteria for weight variability at study initiation
		        (i.e., no significant differences among group means and each individual
		        within 20% of the overall mean body weight).
		    </td>
		</tr>		
	</table>
	<div>&nbsp;</div>
	<div style="text-align:center;">
	    <span style="font-weight:bold;">Table 1. Study Design<sup>a</sup></span>
	</div>
	<tbl_hersh:HershTable1 addStyleNames='centeredObj'/>
	<div style="text-align:center;">
		<sup>a</sup>Data were obtained from <w:DERTextBoxLength name="HA||MaterialsAndMethods>>RefTable1" visibleLength="4"/> page of the study report.
	</div>
	
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>