<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
	xmlns:w="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets"	
	xmlns:tbl="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables"
	xmlns:tbl_hersh="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables.hersh"
	>
	<ui:style>		
	</ui:style>
	
	<g:HTMLPanel width="105ex">
		<table>
		    <col/><col/><col/>
		    <tr>
		       <td>Dose Selection Rationale</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="UA||MaterialsAndMethods>>DoseSelectionRationale>>Html">
				    <p>The dose levels were selected based on the results from a range-finding
				    study <span style="color:firebrick">(MRID [#])</span> in which six ovariectomized female
				    rats/dose group received the test substance in corn oil via
				    gavage at doses of 0, 100, 300, or 1000 mg/kg/day for three consecutive days.
				    At 300 and 1000 mg/kg/day, wet and blotted uterine weights were significantly
				    (p&lt;0.05) increased over vehicle controls, therefore doses of lower than 300 mg/kg/day
				    were used for the main study.</p>
				 </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT></td>
				 <td>Briefly describe any range-finding study, including information regarding the study
				 identification (laboratory report or MRID number), study type (i.e., duration, route of
				 administration, number of animals, species), dose levels, effects, and conclusions.
				 The Test Guideline recommends that the highest dose level not exceed the limit dose of 1000 mg/kg/day.
				  </td>  
		    </tr>
		    <tr>
		        <td>Dose Preparation</td>
		        <td>
		            <w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="UA||MaterialsAndMethods>>DosePrepAndAnalysis>>Html">
		                <p>Dose formulations were prepared
		                <span style="color:firebrick">[daily OR once prior to initiation of treatment]</span>
		                by initially dissolving the appropriate amounts of test substance in
		                (type of vehicle/solvent).
		                The test substance was then mixed with
		                <span style="color:firebrick">[type of vehicle]</span> for dosing.
		                Doses were adjusted daily based on individual body weight measurements.
		                Homogeneity and stability were tested at
		                <span style="color:firebrick">(when, what dose levels, duration, and temperature)</span>. 
		                During the study, samples of dose formulations were analyzed
		                <span style="color:firebrick">(when and at what dose levels)</span> for achieved concentration.</p>
		            </w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
		        </td>
		        <td>Information on dose formulations should include:
		         method and frequency of preparation
		         (i.e., for each dose formulation OR via serial dilution, etc.);
		         storage conditions (i.e., duration and temperature);
		         and dose analysis for homogeneity (sampling method);
		         stability (storage temperature and duration), and achieved concentration
		         (dose levels and when analyzed).
		        </td>  
		    </tr>
		   <tr>
				<td style="text-decoration:underline" colspan="3">Results of Dose Analysis
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Homogeneity:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="UA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>Homogeneity>>Html" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Concentration range as percent of nominal and/or coefficient of variation for different strata (e.g., top, middle, and bottom).</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Stability:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="UA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>Stability>>Html" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Range of values for each temperature and duration tested, expressed as percent of initial (preferable) or percent of nominal concentration.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Concentration:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="UA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>Concentration>>Html" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>
				<td>Range of values expressed as percent of nominal.</td>
			</tr>
		    <tr>
				<td colspan="3">The analytical data indicated that the mixing procedure 
				<w:DERListBoxSC name="UA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>AdequateProcedure"><g:item>was</g:item><g:item>was not</g:item></w:DERListBoxSC>
				adequate. 
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td colspan="3">And that the variation between nominal and actual dosage to the animals
				<w:DERListBoxSC name="UA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>AcceptableVariation"><g:item>was</g:item><g:item>was not</g:item></w:DERListBoxSC>
				acceptable.
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>Describe any deficiencies noted.</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="UA||MaterialsAndMethods>>ResultOfDoseAnalysis>>Deficiencies>>Html" addStyleNames='smallRTA'/></td>				
			</tr>
		   <tr>
				<td>Dosage Administration</td>
				<td>
					<w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="UA||MaterialsAndMethods>>DosageAdministration>>Html">
					    <p>Animals were administered the test formulations and/or EE or vehicle daily via s.c.
					    injection for three consecutive days in a dose volume of 5 mL/kg body weight.
					    Dose volumes were adjusted daily based on the concurrent body weight measurement.
					    </p>
					</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
				</td>
				<td>
				    Summarize dose administration information regarding the test formulations and EE
				    including the route of administration (sc injection preferred, but oral gavage acceptable),
				    dose schedule, and dose volume.  The Test Guideline recommends that doses be administered
				    in a volume of &le;5 mL/kg, unless aqueous solutions were used,
				    in which case the Guideline recommends volumes up to 10 mL/kg body weight.				    				   
				</td>
		    </tr>
		    <tr>
			    <td colspan='3'>The Guideline recommends dosing immature female rats for three consecutive days.
			    A three-day exposure is also recommended for ovariectomized female rats,
			    although a 7 day treatment period may be appropriate as it may improve detection of weakly active substances.
			    If ovariectomized mice are used, a 7 day administration period is strongly recommended to detect any effects.
			    Verify that animals were treated at the same time each day.
			    </td>
			</tr>
		    <tr>
				<td>Statistics:</td>
				<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="UA||MaterialsAndMethods>>Statistics>>Html" /></td>
				<td>
				   	Describe the statistical methods used.  Include a statement as to whether or not the Reviewer considers the analyses used to be appropriate; if inappropriate, provide alternative/rationale. If inappropriate refer to the Guideline for the recommended statistical methods and perform the required analysis. Refer to the SEP for details.			   	
				</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
			    <td colspan='3'>The criterion for statistical significance should be identified (e.g., p &le; 0.05) and groups attaining statistical significance should be denoted. In the DER tables, the asterisk (*) is used as a means of indicating statistical significance. Summary data tables, reporting mean, standard deviation and CV for uterine weights are included for each assay.
				</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>