<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
	xmlns:w="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets"
	
	xmlns:tbl="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables"
	xmlns:tbl_mpa="urn:import:com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.widgets.tables.mpa"
	>
	<ui:style>		
	</ui:style>
	<ui:with field='GDStr' type='com.lmc.der.sixComposers.client.ui.PA_UI.GenderDependantStrings'/>
	
	<g:HTMLPanel width="90ex">
	<table>
	<col style="width:20ex"/><col style="width:70ex"/>
	<tr>
		<td>Mortality and Clinical Examinations:</td>
		<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}">
				<p>All animals were examined <span style="color:firebrick">[frequency; e.g. twice daily]</span>
				for mortality and moribundity.
				Clinical examinations were conducted <span style="color:firebrick">[frequency]</span>.</p>
			</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td>Body Weight:</td>
		<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'>
			Animals were weighed daily prior to dosing.
			</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td>Food Consumption:</td>
		<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'>			
			</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td>Vaginal Opening:</td>
		<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='smallRTA'>
			<p>Beginning on PND <span style="color:firebrick">[22]</span>,
				 all animals were examined daily for onset of vaginal opening.
				Age and weight at on the day of completion of vaginal opening were recorded.</p>
			</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td colspan="2">The Test Guidelines recommend that the appearance of a small "pin hole",
			a vaginal thread, and complete vaginal opening be recorded for all days they are observed.
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td>Estrous Cyclicity:</td>
		<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='bigRTA'>
			<p>Beginning on the day of vaginal opening, up to and including the day of necropsy,
			daily vaginal smears were obtained and evaluated for the presence of leukocytes,
			nucleated epithelial cells, or cornified epithelial cells.
			The vaginal smears were classified as diestrus (predominance of leukocytes mixed with
			some cornified epithelial cells), proestrus (predominance of clumps of round,
			nucleated epithelial cells), or estrus (predominance of cornified epithelial cells).
			The age at first vaginal estrus was recorded.</p>
			</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td colspan="2">A typical cycle consists of two or three days of diestrus, one day of proestrus,
		and one or two days of estrus. The study should normally include detailed information
		on estrous cyclicity for all animals and summary information for the dose groups,
		including (i) the mean age at first vaginal estrus, (ii) the mean cycle length
		for each group, (iii) the percent of each group cycling, (iv) the percent of each group
		cycling regularly, and (v) the stage of the cycle at the time of necropsy.
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td>Sacrifice and Pathology:</td>
		<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='bigRTA'>
			<p>On the day of termination, rats were removed one at a time from their home cages to a separate room
			for euthanasia and terminal procedures so as not to induce stress-related
			responses in other animals which may affect hormone measurements.
			All surviving animals were sacrificed
			<span style="color:firebrick;font-style:italic">(describe method)</span>		
			on PND
			<span style="color:firebrick">[42]</span>
			approximately 2 hours post-dosing.			
			Blood from the trunk of the animals was collected immediately
			into serum separation tubes, processed <span style="color:firebrick">[method]</span>
			, and stored at <span style="color:firebrick">[temperature]
			<span style="font-style:italic">(should be -20&deg;C or colder)</span></span>
			; for subsequent hormone and clinical chemistry evaluations.			
			</p>
			</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td colspan="2">Preferred method of sacrifice is by injectable anesthetic,
			followed by immediate decapitation; carbon dioxide is not an acceptable anesthetic.
			The guideline recommends sacrificesbe completed by 1300 hours
			due to normal diurnal fluctuation in thyroid hormone levels.
			Historical control data should be provided.
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td>Hormone Analysis:</td>
		<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" >
			<p>Total thyroxine (T<sub>4</sub>), and thyroid stimulating hormone (TSH) levels were analyzed using
			<span style="color:firebrick">[assay type; radioimmunoassay (RIA), immunoradiometric assay (IRMA),
			enzyme-linked immunosorbent assay (ELISA), or time-resolved immunofluorescent procedures.]</span>
			</p>
			</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
		</td>
	</tr>
	</table>
	<table>
	<col style="width:20ex"/><col style="width:70ex"/>
	<tr>
		<td>Clinical Chemistry:</td>
		<td>The following CHECKED (&radic;) parameters were examined.</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td colspan="2">
		<table>
		<tr>
			<td style="vertical-align:top">
				<tbl_mpa:MPATableCheckBoxes TblName="ELECTRO_TBL"/>
				* Recommended<br/>based on guideline<br/>890.1450.
			</td>
			<td style="vertical-align:top">
				<tbl_mpa:MPATableCheckBoxes TblName="ENZYM_TBL"/>
			</td>
			<td style="vertical-align:top">
				<tbl_mpa:MPATableCheckBoxes TblName="OTR1_TBL"/>
			</td>
			<td style="vertical-align:top">
				<tbl_mpa:MPATableCheckBoxes TblName="EMPTY5x1_TBL"/>
			</td>
		</tr>		
		</table>
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td>Organ Weights and Histopathology:</td>
		<td>The following CHECKED (&radic;) tissues were collected and weighed.
			The (&radic;&radic;) organs, in addition, were subjected to histological examination.
			<span style="color:firebrick;font-style:italic">(Note if not all collected tissues were examined.)</span>
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td colspan="2">
		<table>
		<tr>
			<td style="vertical-align:top">
				<tbl_mpa:MPATableCheckBoxes TblName="URO_F_TBL"/>				
			</td>			
			<td style="vertical-align:top">
				<tbl_mpa:MPATableCheckBoxes TblName="OTR2_TBL"/>				
			</td>
			<td style="vertical-align:top">
				<tbl_mpa:MPATableCheckBoxes TblName="EMPTY5x2_TBL"/>
			</td>
			<td style="vertical-align:top">
				* Weights required based on<br/>guideline 890.1450<br/>
				** Histopathological examination<br/>required based on guideline 890.1450
			</td>
		</tr>		
		</table>
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td></td>
		<td><w:DERRichTextAreaPUT name="{GDStr.getPath}" addStyleNames='bigRTA'>
			<p>All organs collected, except the thyroid/trachea and uterus were weighed prior to fixation.
				Paired organs (kidneys, adrenals, and ovaries) were weighed together.
				The uterus and cervix were separated from the vagina and weighed.
				The uterus was weighed again following removal of the fluid in the lumen (blotted weight).
			</p>
			<p>
			The ovaries
			<span style="color:firebrick">[left or right]
			<span style="font-style:italic">(should be from the same side of each animal; report any deviations)</span></span>
			and uterus were fixed in 10% buffered formalin and stored in 70% ethanol prior to embedding.
			The thyroid (with parathyroid) and kidneys were fixed in 10% buffered formalin for at least 24 hrs.
			Following fixation, the thyroid was dissected from the trachea.
			All collected tissues were routinely processed into paraffin blocks, sectioned,
			stained with hematoxylin and eosin, and examined microscopically.
			</p>
			</w:DERRichTextAreaPUT>
		</td>
	</tr>
	<tr>
		<td colspan="2">
		This is the information that you would be found in the study report conducted following
		guideline recommendations. Thyroid sections are subjectively evaluated for follicular cell
		height and colloid area, preferably using a five point grading scale (1 = shortest/smallest;
		5 = tallest/largest), and any abnormalities/lesions noted.  At least two sections from each
		of the two lobes of the thyroid should be examined in order to obtain representative sample
		of the thyroid tissue from each lobe.  Note whether ovarian histology included evaluations
		of any abnormalities/lesions (such as ovarian atrophy) and follicular development, including:
		presence/absence of tertiary/antral follicles, presence/absence of corpora lutea, changes
		in corpus luteum development, changes in number of both primary and atretic follicles.
		Five random sections should be evaluated using the method of Smith et al. (1991).
		Uterine histology should document cases of uterine hyper- or hypotrophy as characterized
		by changes in uterine horn diameter and myometrial, stromal, or endometrial gland development.
		The histological assessment should take into account the stage of the estrous cycle of the female
		at the time of necropsy, as ovarian and uterine cellular changes are dependent upon endocrine status.
		Report the histopathological findings in Section II.G. 
		</td>
	</tr>
	</table>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 